tellerium.com 2019-05-16

# Telerium.tv - Start your own livestream free and easy

#### General

Telerium.tv is committed to protecting your privacy when you use the Telerium.tv website. This Privacy Policy informs you of the types of information Telerium.tv collects about you, how that information is used, whether and to whom Telerium.tv discloses it, and the choices you have regarding your personal information. Please read carefully.

#### Collection of Information

Telerium.tv may automatically collect certain aggregated data regarding your use of the website. Aggregated information is anonymous, statistical information that reflects the scope of the website's user base, sales, customer patterns and related site information. In addition, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected by Telerium.tv and other third-party advertising providers during your use of the Telerium.tv website and in serving advertisements to the Telerium.tv website.

Telerium.tv may also use cookies to track and understand the traffic on the Telerium.tv website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that the Telerium.tv website places onto the user's computer hard drive. Cookies identify the user's computer hard drive so that the Telerium.tv website can recognize you the next time you visit.

Third party advertisements (including Google) displayed on or in connection with the Telerium.tv website may also contain cookies set by such advertisers. Telerium.tv does not control these cookies and users of the Telerium.tv website should check the privacy policy of such advertisers to understand whether and how it uses cookies.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

#### Use of Information

If you submit personally identifiable information to Telerium.tv through the Telerium.tv website, then Telerium.tv may use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the site.

Telerium.tv does not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. Telerium.tv may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes.

#### Disclosure of Information

Telerium.tv may share aggregated statistical information and profile information about users of the Telerium.tv website with third-parties, including distributors, vendors, advertisers actual and potential customers and business partners. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Telerium.tv will not share your personally identifiable information with any third-parties for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

Telerium.tv may release personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with any laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, or search warrant.

Telerium.tv also reserves the right to disclose personally identifiable information and/or non-personally-identifiable information that, in good faith, if appropriate or necessary to enforce the Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the Telerium.tv website, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Telerium.tv, our users or others.

#### Changes and updates to this Privacy Notice

This privacy notice may be revised periodically and users are encouraged to review it periodically to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of the Telerium.tv website constitutes your agreement to this privacy notice and any future revisions.
